现在你已经完成了第2课  庆祝一下吧
And now you're done with lesson two. Woohoo. You've made
对于将数据从服务器上传输并展示到
a huge step in being able to transfer data from
你的移动设备上  你已经完成了一大步
a server and bring it all the way down to
现在想象一下你可以将有价值的信息
your device. Think about all the possibilities now of valuable information
带到用户触手可及的地方的
you could bring down to users to be available at
所有可能性  这是非常强大的  说到改变世界这件事
their fingertips. And that's pretty powerful. Speaking about making an impact,
你思考了你要为最终的项目
have you thought about what you're going to do for your
做些什么了没  你可以选择任何你感兴趣的主题
final project yet? You can choose any topic that you want.
在班级的论坛中分享你的想法
Share your ideas in the class discussion forum, and
你也可以在社交网络上分享给你的朋友
you can share with your friends on social media too.
趁着测试的时候  我要在这个Done枕上
Over to beta now, while I take a quick nap
小憩一会  咱们第3节课再见
on this Done pillow. I'll see you in lesson three.